All pirates searching for the treasure One Piece
must brave the second half of the Grand Line.
These wild and dangerous seas are known as the New World.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body became rubber
after eating the gum gum fruit,
sets sail into the New World with his faithful crew.
I'm gonna be the king of the pirates!
Two years have passed since the War of the Best in Marineford.
Reuniting after this special training,
Luffy and his crew continue on to the New World.
The first stop is Fishman Island,
thousands of feet below sea level,
where trouble finds them quickly.
The pirate boy in a straw hat!
It's an emergency!
He must leave the country!
Now, before we run out of time!
I saw him clearly, surrounded by flames,
because, Straw Hat Luffy,
Fishman Island,
our country will be...
destroyed!
The King of the Fishman Island!
Neptune, the God of the Sea!
The King's
Hurry up! We have to move!
C'mon! But quietly!
We can't let them know !
We're all dead if they notice!
We're all dead if they notice.
It's our only chance.
Get on the ship and grab an oar.
We either get out of here today or we die trying.
Come on, faster!
They'll be on top of us in minutes.
We'll never go back to Fishman Island.
Don't let up till we cross the Red Line!
Dammit!
I never got to visit the Marine Cafe!
I never got to either.
It's such a waste.
You idiots get over it already!
Just shut up and keep rowing!
This whole thing is a disaster.
I thought we had made it after we got past the sleeping Kraken.
Then they ambushed us.
At 10,000 meters below.
And with so many sea monsters at their disposal,
there was no way to defend ourselves.
They told us we could join the new Fishman Pirates or we could die.
As if they were really giving us a choice at all.
Who wouldn't pick life over death?
It's absurd.
I mean, each and every one of us is human.
Why would they want us in their ranks anyway?
Goodbye, Mermaid Cafe.
Goodbye.
I told you all to get over it!
We're lucky to even be alive right now!
Really?
They escaped?
I'm afraid so, boss.
My back was turned and they got away.
Humans are always running for it.
You'd think they would have learned by now.
Huh.
Cowardice is in their nature.
You shouldn't let me chew on them when I offered!
Caw, caw, caw!
Mwheehee!
Ugh, what a pain in the ass.
Heh heh heh heh heh heh heh heh heh heh.
No, it's good.
See?
Now we can use them as examples.
Mwheehee!
Then I'll go and drag them back so you can teach them their lesson.
Not this time you won't.
Stay here.
Er, if you say so, boss.
I'll go myself.
Hee hee!
You heard me.
Get the bubble ready.
Boss, you can't take that much power drug at once.
It's dangerous.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
Ah, home sweet home.
Alright, shall we go in?
Ha!
It's huge!
Welcome home, Master!
Can we get you anything?
Oh my gosh!
As in the super famous designer?
I thought he'd be taller!
Man, being famous must be a pain!
What are you talking about? I live for this kind of attention!
When I'm in the water, I'm what you'd call a fashionable starfish.
But on Fishman Island, I'm so much more than that.
Seeing as I'm the president and lead designer for criminal brand clothes.
The products we make are coveted throughout the world.
No country is off limits for our store chains.
Even Dos Goy Panda is...
What's that? There's tons of people!
Hey! Are you listening?
Come on!
And the first floor is a criminal brand store!
Cool!
I wasn't done talking!
You should go check it out!
Okay!
Great! Guys!
What about my story?
Miss, I'm sorry, but I can't accommodate you.
Giving you a discount like that could cost me my job.
Sounds like someone is causing them trouble.
People have some nerve.
Did you not hear me?
I don't care how cute these clothes are.
They're way too expensive.
Speaking of nerve...
I want you to cut the price to 10,000 berries.
But that's less than half the retail price.
You must understand I cannot do that.
It's just as I thought.
Cheapskate!
Hey!
There you are, Nami!
Luffy!
Oh, hi, Kami!
It's been so long.
How have you been?
Good!
All right.
What seems to be the problem here?
Oh, thank goodness you showed up, Monsieur Papagu.
She wants half off, just like her wardrobe.
So you're the one in charge of this extortion ring?
You lower your prices, or I'll lower you.
Oh, monsieur.
You see, there's a thing called brand equity.
Because my designs are popular, they're...
You're not listening.
Okay, okay, I get it!
Look, we're all friends here, aren't we?
I guess I owe you.
For all the help you gave us two years ago.
Whatever you want's free.
Take as much as you can carry.
For real?
Why, thank you!
You know what to do, guys.
Let's bleed them dry.
Yeah!
You're the greatest!
Oh, my goodness, Joe!
They took everything we had!
Oh, come on!
You can cut me some slack!
Talk about a deal!
Or steal!
My, what's all that racket?
Something serious must be happening.
Monsieur!
We have an emergency!
What is it?
It's him!
He is here!
That's kind of vague.
I can't believe it!
Someone pinch me!
Up there in the sky!
You can see him!
We're in the presence of royalty!
What the heck is that?
Some kind of whale?
What is he doing down here in the mower world?
This is my first time seeing him!
This is unheard of!
He doesn't even have guards!
Why is that?
Did something happen?
He's never traveled unattended before!
Something must be wrong in the kingdom!
That has to be it!
He never comes down here unless there's an emergency!
Okay, who's the old guy?
Come on!
How have you not figured this out by now?
It's kind of really important!
The merman in front of you is the king of the Ryugu kingdom!
The ruler of Fishman Island!
The god of the sea!
Neptune!
Indeed I am!
Whoooo!
Oh wow!
Is this dude enormous or what?
I'd rather see a mermaid than a merman!
Will you two shut up!
He's super old!
And he's super hairy too!
Gross!
Keep your observations to yourself!
Kneel down and show some respect!
Can we talk about how cute the whale is?
Is he here because of the humans?
That seems kind of beneath him!
Hmm!
Well Megalo!
Are you certain these are the people you encountered earlier?
Yeah!
Hold on!
I know him!
We met that shark when we were outside!
Oh yeah, right!
I recognize the shirt!
So this is where you went after we saved you!
Hear my words, Straw Hat people!
Huh?
Uh, we're listening!
The reason I am here!
Is to invite you all!
To the Ryugu Palace!
What?
Is that supposed to be a big deal?
Good!
Your pulse is stabilizing!
It looks like you're gonna be fine!
I hope you appreciate all the stuff everyone's done for you, especially them!
Appreciate!
Need more blood, babe?
Just think a part of us will be inside you forever!
Don't worry, Chopper, I don't think I'll ever forget!
What?
I'm happy to hear that!
I can't believe you almost died, though!
Especially from something as silly as a nosebleed!
What would Nami and Robin say?
Nami?
Robin?
No, you can't have a relapse when we're this close!
Hey, get in here!
Splash and Splatta!
Hurry!
Coming!
Is the patient in need of more of our fluids?
If so, just say the word!
He can have anything!
Now, now, you know you have to stay calm, silly!
Leave everything to us!
We'll be here all night!
No!
No means no!
There's no need to be shy!
Let it happen!
Getting worked up is bad for your health!
There's nothing worse for my health in this entire place than you two!
No!
If you guys are famous or something, they do know Monsieur Papagu.
Wait a second, isn't that Soul King?
It is!
Why is this Ryugu place so important?
Don't you know what a palace is?
Here are the details.
Ryugu Palace is like...
Well, it's like a holy icon for the citizens of Fishman Island.
You see, to us, it's a heavenly body where none of us are ever allowed to enter.
But it's so much more than that.
King Neptune, along with the three prince brothers...
...and the mermaid princess, called the place their...
Home!
The royal family lives there, so it's like a house!
Oh...
Ah, Kami, that was dull!
Hey, old man!
Show him some respect!
So this palace of yours, you got any really good food there?
Naturally.
We are prepared to have a banquet in your honor.
We're in!
Why didn't you lead with that?
This is certainly an unexpected development!
It's almost more than my heart can handle!
Good thing that I don't have a heart anymore!
Yo-hoo!
Let's get moving, guys!
The royal family!
I bet they've got tons of treasure laying around!
How did I know that's why you wanted to go?
All right!
Let's roll!
Mm-hmm!
Well, Megalore, I'm counting on you to transport these Straw Hat people to the Ryugu Palace in luxury.
You want us to climb up?
Woohoo!
So cool!
I hope we meet the mermaid princess!
You and me both, buddy!
Hey, what are you doing?
Aren't you guys coming too?
Uh, well, we're not allowed to go.
It's off limits to people like us, right?
Will you just stop complaining and get on?
My dinner is waiting!
And we can't say goodbye already!
That's not a problem!
Right, Grandpa?
You can't just call the king, Grandpa!
Of course not!
Your friends are welcome also!
Hear that?
Grandpa said you can come too!
This can't be happening!
Okay, but please just be polite!
Cool!
Let's go!
It's time to go!
We're not allowed to go!
It's off limits to people like us, right?
Will you just stop complaining and get on?
My dinner is waiting!
And we can't say goodbye already!
That's not a problem!
Right, Grandpa?
You can't just call the king, Grandpa?
Of course not!
Your friends are welcome also!
Hear that?
Grandpa said you can come too!
This can't be happening!
Let's go!
It's time to eat!
Hurry up!
We gotta move!
Roll faster!
We're already living on borrowed time!
If only it weren't so hard to catch a current in the deep sea!
That's why we should have equipped ourselves with paddle wheels!
We weren't ready for the new world after all!
Ah!
Captain!
Look there!
There's something in the water in front of us!
Oh no!
That's...
Horty Jones!
He found us!
We're screwed!
Hold on!
See his hands?
Those are handcuffs!
Why's he stuck in those things?
You don't think he plans to fight us like that, do you?
He's gone!
Where the hell did he go?
No!
Get up!
He's coming back around!
He's staring at the board!
How the hell is he this fast?
What do we do now, boss?
Take them out!
There's only one of them after all!
Oh no!
What now?
You're not the first fish man I've fought against, and I've done your dirty work.
Now it's my chance to return the favor!
You're only a damn fish!
So let me teach you a lesson!
Don't mess with humans!
Captain, no!
No!
I'm not done yet!
Yeah, you are.
We were tough before, but we're unbeatable with this.
Our power drug, the energy steroid.
Fish men are naturally ten times stronger than humans,
but that hasn't made a strong enough impression.
However, with just one pill, we can double our strength,
and finally strike some terror into their cowardly little hearts.
I don't know if I'd go as far as our boss,
but doubling the dose and doubling the effect has its benefits,
even if it does shorten our lifespan.
Well, we aren't afraid of dying if we can realize our dream, right?
Wait!
What the hell is he doing now?
Get away from the mask, you freak!
That's why!
The handcuffs!
He warned him to prove that he doesn't need his hands to sink us!
Not only did humans kill Fisher Tiger, but they also dashed Arlong's dreams.
The dark chain of events that have cursed our race end now.
That is our purpose as the new Fishman Pirates!
Set them adrift in the new world.
Okay.
End now.
That is our purpose as the new Fishman Pirates!
Set them adrift in the new world.
Okay, but some of those guys are still alive.
Shouldn't we kill them all first?
No, they have a purpose.
You'll see.
Those of you who are getting away with just cuts and bruises
will live to send a message.
Tell the people up above what happened to you in the sea.
Let them know who did this to you.
You've seen my strength firsthand,
so don't spare a single detail.
Because once we've liberated Fishman Island
from the gutless god of the sea, Neptune,
we'll be coming to drag you humans to the bottom of these depths!
I promise you that!
And the Fishman will stand on top of the world
as the supreme species!
Luffy and friends accept King Neptune's invitation
and head for Ryugu Palace.
However, Luffy is tempted by the smell of food
and leaves the group in search of something to eat.
What?
Wandering the palace,
he soon comes upon an enormous tower
with a sturdy sealed door.
What is the story behind the strange weapons lodged in its side?
On the next One Piece,
the Ryugu Palace,
taken by the shark that they saved,
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!